

Why would I make a great engineer at your company?

I'm a full-stack engineer specializing in Al-driven web applications. My experience spans startups to established companies, where I've engineered Al chat interfaces, custom SaaS apps, and LLM agents. Combining expertise in Al and full-stack development with product exploration skills, I bridge advanced technology and practical applications to drive business growth and user engagement.

Experience

Full Stack Engineer · Luna.ai - VC backed Al Start-Up

Sept. 2023 - Present · Remote, San Francisco

- Implemented complex LLM pipelines and agents using fine-tuned LLMs, RAG, and various prompt engineering techniques (e.g chain-of-thought and few-shot learning).
- Implemented a custom AI chat interface using React, which improved our user activation rate by 4x.
- Developed and maintained a custom A/B testing framework to measure LLM pipeline output quality, leveraging MixPanel, Segment, Express.js, and TypeScript.
- Built a custom software using React, Tailwind, and Next.js.

Front End Engineer · Fledge - Cloud ERP Software

Jun. 2022 - Sept. 2023 · Enschede, The Netherlands

- Led a team of 12 developers in modernizing legacy ERP software to a cloud-based service.
- Mentored 10 junior developers in Angular web development and Agile methodologies
- Developed custom ERP front ends using Angular, RxJS, and NgRx.
- Collaborated with stakeholders to define and implement product requirements.

Full Stack Engineer · PositiveDigits - Custom E-commerce Software

Jun. 2020 - Jun. 2022 · Den Bosch, The Netherlands

- Implemented DevOps best practices using Terraform, Kubernetes, and Docker for efficient e-commerce platform deployment and
- Developed custom e-commerce storefronts using TypeScript, PHP, and Tailwind CSS.

Full Stack Engineer · Acorel - SAP Consultancy

Feb. 2020 - Jun. 2020 · Den Bosch, The Netherlands

• Improved the product recommendation system of Intergamma, utilizing Neo4j and Java Spring Boot.

Front End Engineer · JouwWeb - Website Builder SaaS

Sept. 2018 - Jan. 2019 · Eindhoven, The Netherlands

 Developed multiple configurable templates using React, for a website builder. Now used by over 100,000 active customers

Links

→ Visit my LinkedIn

→ Visit my GitHub

Tech Stack



My Skills

Full Stack Engineering
Multi Agent Systems
Natural Language Processing
Data Engineering
Speech Processing

My Interests

Artificial Intelligence

Psychology

Music Production I

Avid Reader

Travel Lover

Languages

English (C2, Proficient)

Dutch (Native)

Korean (A1, Beginner)

Education

M.Sc. Interaction Technology · University of Twente. - GPA: 8/10

2021 - 2023 · Enschede, The Netherlands

Relevant Coursework: Natural Language Processing, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Human-Computer Interaction, and Conversational Agents.

Thesis (conducted at 부산대학교, Korea): Research in Human-Al collaborative models. Grade: 8.5/10

B.Sc. Computer Science · Avans Hogeschool - *GPA*: 7.5/10

2016 - 2020 · Enschede, Netherlands

Relevant Coursework: Natural Language Processing, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Human-Computer Interaction, and Conversational Agents.

Minor (conducted at 부경대학교, Korea): Exchange study which focused on the understanding of Korean language and culture.

B.A. Guitar · Conservatoire of Music Amsterdam - Propedeuse

2015 - 2016 · Amsterdam, Netherlands

Studied the (electric) guitar. Extensive coursework in composing, producing, and performing (pop) music.

Publications

Leenders, R., Camin, P., Velner, E., & Theune, M. (2022). Björn: An interrogation simulator. In Proceedings of the first international conference on hybrid human-machine intelligence. IOS Press. Retrieved from https://ebooks.iospress.nl/doi/10.3233/FAIA220213